The Ritual Killer is a mystery, thriller, action film directed by George Gallo.
Unable to process the death of his daughter, Detective Boyd embarks on a hunt for a
serial killer who murders according to a brutal tribal ritual: Muti.
The only person who can help Boyd is Professor Mackles, an
anthropologist who hides an unspeakable secret.
The line between sanity and madness thins as Boyd
goes deeper into the killer’s world.
Dr. Mackles, played by Morgan Freeman.
Detective Lucas Boyd, played by Cole Hauser.
Randoku, played by Vernon Davis.
Captain Marchand, played by Peter Stormare.
Inspector Mario Lavazzi, played by Giuseppe Zeno.
Detective Kersch, played by Murielle Hilaire.
The Ritual Killer is a 2023 American
action-thriller film directed by George Gallo.
It stars Morgan Freeman and Cole Hauser.
It was released by Screen Media and Redbox Entertainment on March 10, 2023.
The tone is dark and emotional and mind_bending.